Good morning. He has something he wants to say about school shootings. Here is his extra point.
Another high school shooting yesterday, this one in Florida. 17 dead, the last report I saw.
And everybody sends their thoughts and prayers again because that works so well.
This is the 18th high school shooting in America this year, and we have 10 and a half months to go.
We've had 290 since 2013. We average about one a week, but there's just nothing we can do.
If there was a Muslim or a Mexican doing the shooting, how many new laws and how much money would we spend then to stop the madness?
But since it's almost always a white kid, there's just nothing we can do.
America has 5% of the world's population and yet 31% of the world's mass shootings.
We're worried about people coming to this country. They should be worried about us going to theirs.
Australia had four mass shootings between 87 and 96.
They passed stricter gun laws and haven't had a single mass shooting since.
And here I thought, guns don't kill, people do. Is this the people we are?
Last time I said we need to find a way to stop a nut with a gun, and that's all I said.
I get an email saying, I'm saving my last bullet to put it right between your eyes.
Just another responsible gun owner in America, and I'm taking all bets, he's a white guy.
So there's just nothing we can do.
I'm Dale Hanson. It's getting harder to enjoy the day.
Thank you.